Benjamin Gaither

Cropwell, Alabama, United States

mattgaither2@gmail.com

2055050759

linkedin.com/in/benjamin-gaither-88732794

Summary

I have been working in customer service for the past 2 years and have learned that I would love to get into software engineering.

I have attended a MERN Full Stack bootcamp and have learned HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL, NoSQL, GraphQL, and React.

I love to learn new thing and I catch on really quickly. I am in the process of teaching myself Python.

Experience



Flex Team Specialist

Shipt

Jan 2022 - Present (8 months +)

Experience Team

Shipt

Feb 2021 - Jan 2022 (1 year)

- Utilize Email, chat and phone communication with members and shoppers
- Collected customer and shopper feedback, and made suggestions for new or more streamlinedfeatures
- Educated and assisted shoppers on their daily duties
- Quickly solved unexpected problems and ensure orders are accurate and on time
- Assist shoppers when possible with updating applications
- Helped troubleshoot the app and website when issues were affecting members and shoppers andreported the issues if they could not be resolved
- Helped outsourced agents and other experience team members with interactions and took escalatedcalls

Education



Michigan State University

Full Stack Bootcamp, Web Development

Mar 2022 - Sep 2022

The Full Stack in this Bootcamp was HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL, NoSQL, Progressive web applications, and React.

Jefferson State Community College

Associate's degree, Business Administration and Management, General

Aug 2020 - Present

Pell City High School

Benjamin Gaither - page 1

2006 - 2009

Skills

Google Docs • Google Sheets • Genesys Cloud • Works well in a team • Customer Service • JSON • JavaScript • React.js • API Testing

Benjamin Gaither - page 2